<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[NO APPLES]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>NO APPLES</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 05:10:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 05:10:55 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[ETC TASKING CANVAS]]></title><description><![CDATA[
All ETC members must display an allegiance to the Temple—remember the careful line that is being tread. At the same time, use this opportunity to spread awareness of the historical premise and theological precedence of the ETC, especially among visiting clergy. If completed, must be a group thread, ideally a member-run event. The boringly human part of predictive, "artificial" intelligence—encode hundreds of hours of footage tracking Inquisitors and explaining their movements to help categorize and archive footage. RCA also seems to be allowing some use of their personal surveillance system, or debating merging it with the student-run system If completed, thread must decide if student-collected surveillance will be merged with RCA's or not. How did an organization come to be so compromised? Finish or further investigations into its members, and provide the information, freely and with a display of proactivity, to the Inquisition. UNTRACEABLE DELETION Inside the halls of the Base, the Inquisition is breathing down the Federation's neck. No solider has been killed yet (or the Federation is doing a great job of hiding it?), but the tension might suffocate them all the same. There are some tasks—removal, deletion, moving things...that are better done by hands the red robes aren't watching as closely. Not available to cadets of Alvaran descent. TIGHTEN RANKS Not everyone in the ETC can be trusted. As the organization grows, it's important to generate a core committee. Who falls in the actual governing body, and who winds up as more of a standing member? How might they accept new members? What does this "union of Valkyries" look like, and how will it run? If completed, thread must name Lance's successor. AUDIT MEETINGS The ETC has decided that it will retain its own auditing of public Temple and Lotus Tower meetings, and also have voices therein that can begin sowing pressure against the Temple through legitimate channels of grievance. In the winter, there is an announcement the administration makes regarding the "biotech attack" campus experienced... The announcement also contains a packet on Sabotage and Subversion of RCA, Security Report which is redacted, but seems to suggest that RCA has identified critical points at which outsiders—including heretics, though the positioning of these redactions suggest...something else, too—are entering onto campus. Notably, RCA states that intruders are using technology such as HEXLIGHT or other advanced, unknown magitech, to mimic the appearance of RCA cadets when operating. This news, more than anything else, shakes the campus. Simmered-down tensions between Federation and Alvaran students threaten to rise again. WHAT COMES OUT OF THIS? what information is revealed? what balance is disrupted?
links strange tokens (announced as "biotech attack") to HERETICAL ACTIVITY
outsider activity becomes increasingly pressing as a security concern
tightened biosecurity = more fun room to play with increasingly invasive surveillance Intruders at RCA. Or wait, are those the students in that smuggling group? It doesn't matter—this checkpoint has to be enforced, they can be taken to campus security, and if they are students, they would just comply. If completed, thread must permanently injure a non-ETC member. In the middle of winter, just ahead of the bustling crowds of the Winter Games, the ETC wins its first (perhaps entirely symbolic) "victory"—the Inquisition, they say, agrees grail pikes may be a disturbance to the Lotus Tower's daily functioning, allows them to see their (re)movement under the Temple's jurisdiction, who then enables students to begin their deconstruction. It is the first time in history this has happened, though perhaps a strange thing to celebrate when Loehr itself seems to be going up in flames. Tianku, according to word of mouth, was at this meeting, and then left halfway out of, apparent, boredom.
the goal of a scene is to change something.
ideally, information is revealed; power shifts between key players; a balance is disrupted. themes are patterns: dots connect, the plot progresses.
a question is asked, setting up the next scene.
potential exploration of guilt/ shame especially after SSR events. maybe a former pryde member seeks them out &amp; is looking to repent. could swing the other way. potential for serious conflict.NPC QUEST, SOCRACTIC PARADOX.
AS SEEN IN: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://sunstrike.jcink.net/index.php?showtopic=2881&amp;st=0&amp;#entry40277" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://sunstrike.jcink.net/index.php?showtopic=2881&amp;st=0&amp;#entry40277" target="_self">PAPARAZZI MURDER MYSTERY</a>
PEOPLE OF INTEREST: ADELA COURTWATER, SANYA SHAW
Red Crescent Academy's—the largest in the world's—database of abnormalities, accessed by students, Valkyries, and instructors regularly, was cracked open without notice being taken. Information there was used to create directives to attack specific targets. The directive was then placed into an exoskeletal device, similar but vastly different, to common Valkyrie combat assistant devices, manufactured by dozens of corporations, from Baifu to Estech. A remote activation was triggered. (There are more speculative facts, also presented neatly. Herectics will be killed and forgiven. The eve of the Solstice, of all days. RCA itself, a target.)
What remains: the only group of people capable—of the machinery, of the software, of the data collections without a single data "breach"—are Valkyries themselves. The exact who and why are always ambiguous things that cannot be dissected by mere iteration. Even still, this is dangerous knowledge. It is the kind of information that cannot leave the room. It is the kind of information that— "—will collapse the trust in the globalized Valkyrie system as we know it." So says Cross.
strange tokens and how exactly they came to be connected to pryde, were they came from [pending whether adela/sanya share depends on where the focus of the research goes] the transfer of keymaster from lance to elijah, how that happened, how elijah became compromised (this could be our original tie in for the link to the dissolution of book club somehow. it's possible.) confrontation, could be more violent or can also be lowkey/sad. can set up some reconnaisance scenes. book club &amp; etc members: cass (vc), sanya shaw, mahdia zanbeketc gets 'thwarted' on the first pass by cass, but rca provides evidence that cass blew up magitech in red light green light ETC put on a harsh deadline to resolve this by RCA?sef and ethe are going to look through a lot of video footage and get things that are pretty (yikes for rca if it gets into the hands of the inquisitors) such as ethe (?) fainted but 'hexlight' did not go away to reveal the actual person. and potentially on a certain april day, lance went into the dressing room, someone else entered...and only one came out. chance are they would delete this but also keep it on a usb as back up cuz that isn't something they want the inquisitors to have but it isn't data they want to be completely gone eitherindividual member trailing — why pryde had an anti-alvaran slant in the first place - naturally it's probably because of fed favouring but there's definitely something to sink teeth into herepossible looking into where pryde's funding was coming from? we know pryde was funded by alumni and resulted in fitzgerald getting shut down, so i think following the money could also be a pretty compelling angle to look at investigating into connections to valkyries from the pryde - probably best suited to people who are originally working on base 64 and suchVOLUNTEERS FOR NON-ETC PERMANENT INJURY:
lio, mana, kazi, nino, yuzhe, tiger and konstantinThere are some heads that are different and odd (vivi's mother for example). while removing the pikes, anyone wanna maybe...see if we can do up close horrific inspections to to potentailly find a cause? People gawking / crowd forming to watch, having to interact with public perception. Vignette style?? you are able to define what "leader" even means or is capable of. think about organizational structures in real life. general members? voting members? who is accountable to who and how? ETC has already been running for a while. if making a rudimentary discussion about "what it should do," consider when that would even take place given the things that have already been accomplished. that being said, the submitted thread could very easily be a nascent-idea thread, pre-ETC itself, which may take the edge and weight off of it and allow for rapid-fire discussion, and really capture the chaos of "making" something entirely new. at the same time, is "Executive Task Committee" itself in its nascent form something that wants to continue? how to bridge the present (doing work), with the future (? valkyrie independence? a union?). does the committee want to self-sustain and evolve, or will it plan its own obsolescence for something new? and finally, remember the end product of your desires cannot be made right now—likely, not even within several years of the ETC's founding. what form can best meet the present, while seeding the future? PANDORA — 14:58 re: the topic of leading ETC, thinking more thru and: - open to u guys Not Wanting it as a PC. given that well. consequences may be Extremely Dire, OOC expectations may be High, and in some cases looks like IC desire doesnt really exist (Sef for example?) ....in that case feel free to collaboratively develop an NPC as well in yr ranks thread (or other threads) and ship them off to me. ill get lonely when the captains are gone ![:Sadge:](https://cdn.discordapp.com/emojis/936564636763975710.webp?size=56) . this could give u flexibility in creating a "council" (as seems to be the desire) w/o worrying abt how leadership affects those picks as well. i have no preference either way. - looked through the member list, and given lance's preferences i listed last time (diplomacy stat highly valued), think he'd be most comfortable with either Ethe Serettis, or Samira Batai. potentially also interested in Sanya Shaw (doesnt know well enough or as well as the first two), Sef Novosi (thinks is too anti-Temple), or Anima Blair (doesn't seem reliable), the rest he doesnt know well/at all.
more so a matter of citizenship than descent/ethinicity so to speak. tensions are focused on federation vs alvara — students from other countries e.g. medved may not be subject to said restrictions.suitable for 3+ PARTICIPANTS. see relevant SCENE NOTES.
essentially, a set of interconnected scenes that interact with each other either on-screen or off-screen, playing out in a loose chronological order. e.g. CHAR A &amp; CHAR B post 1 time each, capturing a moment during the "leadup" of an investigation. CHAR C &amp; D follow up with a 3rd and 4th post where they raid and search an area, having reconvened with A &amp; B off-screen in-between the two scenes.development-style post within a group setting. focused on a character, activity, etc. likely minimal interaction, but posts within the thread are all connected through a predetermined theme or setting.the usual play by post. u know the drill.suitable for 3+ PARTICIPANTS. round-based event format, with updates every ~72 hours from a DM. no set turn/posting order.fuck it we ball. get a bunch of people in a room and go crazy.think it would be interesting if we really incorporated selflessness/pride as themes throughout whatever event we run, whether that be as a dev opportunity or as a way to showcase the way the etc might be perceived by fellow cadets/visiting clergy.lea di merlo — Yesterday at 21:17
for fall equinox...... harvest festival! i think it would be fun if there's a tradition of giving away your spring clothes (selflessness) + buying yourself New, fall clothes to wear (pride?) so we could have etc running stalls for donation drives + selling new clothes and other vanity items (maybe lotus tower-provided), can have ppl bargaining and trying to see who can sell the most shit. also can double as a popular gardening club (or any gardener) venue bc they can add their fall harvest to the harvest table (jus a big ass table with incense, lekh, mirrors, and donated fruits/veggies that ppl pray to lol) dead perseise — Yesterday at 21:30
i think that's brilliant!! it could also give cute tie ins of seniors "donating" some of their old stuff to juniors (emotionally repressed religiously significant keepsakes or w/e) i noted this in the doc but i think it could be interesting if we explored the concept of selflessness/pride in how the etc is perceived also ... some cadets/clergy seeing it as a dangerous venture that they're glad someone is taking on (but not them) vs some others thinking it a project born from hubris safi — Yesterday at 21:32
i think we could probably also do a raffle/fundraiser for some really expensive items some students have,,, dead perseise — Yesterday at 21:33
we r raffling off lance's family sword replica safi — Yesterday at 21:33
all money goes towards loehran charities that are helping with victims off the inquistion
LMFAO lea di merlo — Yesterday at 21:34
dia will not suppport this..... but if its advertised as regular charity and then given to victims of the inquisition..... what can she do really... dead perseise — Yesterday at 21:34
generally tho id love to help run the event 👉 👈 am a big fan of creating religious &amp; cultural traditions &amp; seeing how they mesh also you know how the tortoise festival went from charity -&gt; gluttony on nightfall. what if selflessness -&gt; pride change involves like. your best clothes &amp; festive facepaint etcetera ... The RCA wants nothing to do with organizations that are exclusive, alumni-funded or powered, or attempt to have secret rituals of faith. The Academy is pushing students instead to seek worship, as is in the Lekh, openly and ardently. You've heard of a certain "book club" that needs to be removed. ...There are parts of the investigation the RCA believes would be "unnecessary" to show the Inquisition. You understand. Get rid of the evidence. Not available to cadets of Alvaran descent.
some interesting hooks potentially with the surveillance-based hooks and prompts within the internships - links wip]]></description><link>etc-tasking-canvas.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 SUNSTRIKE/ETC TASKING CANVAS.canvas</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 05:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>